Inaba!
I'm sorry!
I'm really sorry about what I said!
Kiriyama's suffering right now,
so I couldn't think of anything but that.
And then my desires got unleashed...
You've let me down, Inaba.
I never thought you'd turn your back on a friend.
Well, you couldn't help yourself.
But I should've been able to.
This is hard on you, too, but I still...
It doesn't bother me at all.
You only said it because you were worried about Yui.
But please, don't ask me to go to the club room or Yui's.
I need some alone time, too.
I...
I definitely want you to spend time with us.
If you need help with anything, just ask me.
I want you back with us as soon as possible.
It's like we're losing everybody, one by one.
I think Inaban feels worse about what she said to Yui than what you said to her.
Inaban's more sensitive than she looks.
So it's for the best that I leave her alone, huh?
I'm really worried about Yui, too.
If she misses too many classes,
she might get held back a year.
It's only been a week.
I don't think that's much of a problem yet.
But if this continues...
It feels so...
empty.
Inaba should come back if we give her some time.
For the time being, we should focus on Kiriyama.
But Yui doesn't want to see us right now.
Yesterday...
If her mom were there, she would've let us in.
Even if we went to her room, what would we do then?
Either way, we can't do anything if we don't go.
Kiriyama might be feeling better today.
But if one of our desires gets unleashed while we're there,
it'll turn out the same as last time.
Didn't we say the same things yesterday?
What are we supposed to do?
There's not much we can do.
I understand what Yui's saying,
but if she keeps this up,
Balloon Vine might do something.
I...
I don't think anything good can
come from our current situation.
But Yui'll just get hurt if she goes outside.
Who knows what she might do to the people around her?
Then again, you can say the same about us.
But Kiriyama looked so sad that she could die!
Can't you think of anything other than how Yui feels right now?
Try thinking about what would happen if you did something!
Saving Kiriyama right now is what's important!
Oh, so we're back to your "I have to save everyone I can see" mindset now?
Can you really solve this with your selfless crap?
How can you say that?
Don't you want to save Kiriyama?
Hold—Taichi... Aoki...
I want to save her, but I don't know what to do!
Then why don't we go see Kiriyama right now?!
We go there, and then what?!
We'll make something happen!
We couldn't make anything happen the last time or the time before that!
So what?!
Sitting here and talking won't change anything!
How many times are we going to do this?!
Cut it out already, you two!
Aoki, calm down!
I've had enough.
I'm going by myself today.
What? Who put you in charge?!
We're doing it my way this time.
I can save Kiriyama.
Who do you think you are?!
You think you can do anything?
It worked when we were switching personalities!
And you couldn't do a single thing!
Aoki, calm down!
You too, Taichi!
That won't work every time.
Do you have to play hero all the time?
Who's "playing" hero?
I'm saving Kiriyama!
Saving her?!
You're just a selfish freak that can't stand seeing Yui sad!
So what?!
It beats being useless like you!
What'd you call me?
I said to stop it, you two!
Taichi, stop being so full of yourself!
Aoki, stop being jealous!
Is either of you really thinking about Yui?
You just don't want to see her hurt!
Don't get in my way!
Out of my way!
Are you okay, Nagase?!
See what I mean?!
You hurt people like that because you're such a selfish freak!
I said too much. Sorry.
It's not your fault, Taichi.
It was just an unleashed desire.
It's okay.
When I pushed Nagase out of the way, my desires were unleashed.
But what about before that?
Was that really...
My desire wasn't really unleashed until...
Don't get in my way!
Even when my desires aren't unleashed, I'm...
Onii-chan, is something wrong?
Your room's all dark.
Asleep?
No. Did you need something?
You've been in your room all day, so I thought you might be sick.
Caught a cold?
It's nothing.
It's better if you don't come near me right now.
Did you get into a fight with your girlfriend?
Oh, you did.
That's no good.
You boys are stronger, so you have to take the fall.
You're right.
Hurry and make up, okay?
Good night.
Even my sister's worried about me.
What the heck is wrong with me?
Oh.
This must be how Kiriyama feels.
Oh, Mom?
So you're seeing him again tonight?
Yeah, I'll be fine by myself.
No problem at all!
Should I have come today?
If my desires get unleashed again, I might do something even worse.
Don't think about anything.
Focus on class.
Don't think... Don't think...
Morning, Taichi.
Yeah.
Ao—
Taichi!
You're going to the club room, right?
Aren't you?
Oh, Inaban!
You're going to the club room, right?
Sorry, not going today, either.
See you.
I'm going straight home today, too.
Sorry.
Hey.
You guys have been acting weird.
Not really.
We're always like this.
Well, you are always off in your own little world.
Kiriyama from Class 1-1.
She still hasn't come back, right?
Seems that way.
I don't mean to pry,
but did someone screw something up?
No, nothing like that.
Glad to hear it.
As you know, the first-year class will be going on a field trip this Friday.
Today, we're forming groups and
going over the schedule for our trip.
Sounds boring.
Isn't it just any old field trip?
Where the heck is Gossan?
Is he leaving everything to us students?
Isn't that like teacher negligence or something?
Well, maybe.
At least we have Queen Fujishima!
Man, she's as beautiful as ever today.
Were you one of her fans?
Are you some kind of masochist?
I'd like to start by organizing groups for the trip's main event, making curry rice.
We'll have six groups with five people in each.
Other classes will also be using the facilities.
Isn't six groups too many?
Wouldn't more people per group be better?
What are you people talking about?
This moment will be a part of your youth.
Sure, you could just spend it playing around with your friends.
But isn't there something more important?
That's right.
I'm talking about...
Love!
With fewer members per group,
helping each other becomes a necessity.
Working together to accomplish one goal.
Our hearts, connecting!
Our hands, touching!
Do you dare deprive yourself of such an opportunity?
So what will it be?
The six groups of five?
Or do you still want bigger groups?
Six groups, please!
Six groups here, too, Fujishima Nee-san!
Very good.
For now, form groups with two to three boys or girls in each.
If you already have someone in mind,
feel free to form your entire group now.
Go!
Let's be in the same group, Yaegashi.
Sure. I don't mind.
And let's get Fujishima-san to join our group!
Er... um...
You're probably planning to get Nagase and Inaba in our group,
but I won't let you!
You get enough good moments with them in your club,
so you're helping me out this time.
I haven't had any good moments.
And I think Fujishima might be too much for you to handle.
That's how I like it!
And why are you saying it like you know something about her that I don't?
I have my reasons.
We should be in the same group, Inaban.
Especially since something might happen.
Get away from me. Seriously.
Do I have to repeat myself?
You don't have to say it like that.
It's for your own good.
I'm thinking about what's best for you, too, you know!
But my thinking is right.
We don't know that!
Hey, Yaegashi...
Keep it down, stupid!
Did you just call me stupid? You did, didn't you?
Calm down!
You know what I mean!
Just get away from me already!
I'm going to the bathroom.
Nagase!
Inaba-san, Nagase-san, and I will be in the same group.
What's the big idea?
I want you and Nagase-san to get along.
If you don't, the whole class will feel uncomfortable.
You don't have a right to tell me what to do.
Defending the peace and love of the
class is a class president's responsibility.
That doesn't give you a right to decide this!
It does.
Because I'm...
the class president!
Damn...
I didn't know she was defending our love, too!
It's fine with you, right, Yaegashi-kun?
Me?!
You're in a group with Watase-kun?
Then Nagase-san, Inaba-san, Yaegashi-kun, Watase-kun, and I will be one group.
Okay?
Why are you asking me?
You don't have—
Quiet!
No objections!
Let's go with that group!
Then it's settled.
Any other groups of five yet?
Yaegashi, I'll get you a soda or something.
Two of them!
Inaban!
I'll be in the club room.
Don't tell me...
Balloon Vine?!
Oh, Yaegashi?
What are you doing here?
Uh... not much.
Can you believe this?
Another teacher was complaining about how this podium wobbles like crazy.
I asked them to change it for me, but they told me to do it myself!
That's not in my job description as a teacher.
There should be a spare in storage, but that's so far away.
Thanks for offering to help, Yaegashi.
Don't mention it. It's not like I had anything else to do.
Doing this alone would've sucked.
I guess the two of us need to clean this place up a bit first.
Hey.
You're feeling down, aren't you?
No, I'm not.
You can't convince me when you look that depressed.
I know.
You were dumped.
Was it Nagase?
Inaba?
Or maybe, Kiriyama?
No, you've got the wrong—
You should talk to your friends about it.
What?
Talk to your friends about it.
Oh, don't ask me for advice!
High school romance isn't my kind of thing.
But you know, talking to your
friends usually solves a lot of stuff.
But if I talked to my friends, they'd get hurt.
Huh?
Isn't hurting and causing problems for
each other what being friends is all about?
Or is it that?
Like a love triangle sort of thing?
Oh, I see!
It's better if you sit down and talk
those kinds of things through, too.
If you're really friends, everything should work out just fine when you take a direct approach.
I mean, sure, sometimes you'll mess up,
but it's better than letting things get awkward and regretting it forever.
Messing up is definitely better, right?
I guess...
You can't really call yourselves
friends if you never get into a fight.
What do they say?
"If you keep playing it safe, you'll lose something really important."
Oh, damn! I sound like a real teacher, don't I?
Admit it. You're moved, too!
Right?
I would be if you hadn't said that last part.
Oh, Fujishima! Back from
that thing about the field trip?
Keep up the good work.
And perfect timing.
Could you listen to what Yaegashi has to say?
What?
Huh?!
I was just telling Yaegashi about the
importance of talking to your friends.
So could you listen to what he has to say?
He's got a lot on his plate right now.
Yaegashi-kun is no friend of mine.
He's my rival.
What?!
What kind of relationship trouble is this?!
So?
I'm thinking about how to say this.
What would you do if you ran the risk of hurting someone if you talked to them?
Just not talk to them.
But if you didn't talk to them, you couldn't do something.
Then just talk to them.
But then you might hurt them—
All right then, Yaegashi-kun.
Which is more important?
Not hurting them?
Or talking and accomplishing something?
Which of those two is more important to you?
Why not think about that?
If you sit down and decide
what's most important to you,
things might work out better than you thought.
Conversely, there are probably a lot of things that won't go well if you don't decide.
By the way,
I think people hurting each other is inevitable.
But what you think about that is up to you.
Sorry.
It's me.
Oh, what's up?
In other words, you've got love trouble.
Leave it to me.
Any other questions?
No. Go help them out.
Let me know if you ever need any help again.
If it's related to our class in any way, I'll lend a hand.
What are you, Fujishima?
Me?
I'm... Well, let's see...
Right now, I'd say a missionary of love.
Everyone is worried about us.
We were only thinking about ourselves as the CRC,
but there's more to this world than just the five of us.
It's so obvious, but I have to say it.
Nagase!
That's so mean, Taichi!
Talking man-to-man in a place like this is like youth at full throttle!
So if you don't mind, can I stay by your side?
Is that place really the most important thing to you?
How can you say that?!
Shut up!